Guide to the New York University Portrait Files MC.319
New York University Archives
- W
  - Wolf, William, undated (Box 115, Folder 47)
  - Wolf, Woody, undated (Box 115, Folder 48)
  - Wolfe, Bob, undated (Box 115, Folder 49)
  - Wolfe, George C., undated (Box 115, Folder 50)
  - Wolfe, Gerald, undated (Box 115, Folder 51)
  - Wolfe, Julia Elizabeth, undated (Box 115, Folder 52)
  - Wolfe, Max, 1954 (Box 115, Folder 53)
  - Wolfe, Thomas, 1954 (Box 115, Folder 54)
  - Wolfe, Tom, 1981, 1983 (Box 115, Folder 55)
  - Wolff, Hannah, undated (Box 115, Folder 56)
  - Wolff, William Sr., circa 1945 (Box 115, Folder 57)
  - Wolfman, Bernard, 1987 (Box 115, Folder 58)
  - Wollett, Donald H., undated (Box 115, Folder 59)
  - Wong, Karen, undated (Box 115, Folder 60)
  - Wood, Ernest, undated (Box 115, Folder 61)
  - Wood, Robert A., undated (Box 115, Folder 62)
  - Wood, Wallace, undated (Box 115, Folder 63)
  - Woodbury, Dr. Max A., undated (Box 115, Folder 64)
  - Woodruff, Hale, 1948-1949, 1960, 1966 (Box 115, Folder 65)
  - Woodruff, Lewis B., undated (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Woodruff, Theresa, 1982
    - Photographs (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - Negatives (Box 124, Folder 2)
  - Woodward, M. Lobell Jr., 1985 (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Wooley, Mary, 1927 (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Woolf, Virginia (Box 124, Folder 3)
  - Woolley, Patrick, undated (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Word, Dan, undated (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Work, Harold K., 1954 (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Wortis, S. Bernard, 1961 (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Wreen, Peggy, undated (Box 116, Folder 9)
  - Wright, Bruce, undated (Box 116, Folder 10)
  - Wright, Christina, undated (Box 116, Folder 11)
  - Wright, Lindsey, undated (Box 116, Folder 12)
  - Wright, Mark, 1986 (Box 116, Folder 13)
  - Wright, Orville Jr., 1965 (Box 116, Folder 14)
  - Wright, Paul, 1989 (Box 116, Folder 15)
  - Wright, Rita, undated (Box 116, Folder 16)
  - Wright, Robert F., undated (Box 116, Folder 17)
  - Wright, Stephen J., undated (Box 116, Folder 18)
  - Wright, Walter, undated (Box 116, Folder 19)
  - Wrightsman, Charles Bierer, 1963 (Box 116, Folder 20)
  - Wrightsman, Jayne Kirkman, undated (Box 116, Folder 21)
  - Wsaver, Charles, undated (Box 116, Folder 22)
  - Wugen, William, 1959 (Box 116, Folder 23)
  - Wusthoff, Richard, 1973 (Box 116, Folder 24)
  - Wyatt, Samuel, 1967 (Box 116, Folder 25)
  - Wyganowski, Dr. Staneslaw, undated (Box 124, Folder 6)
  - Wygod, Martin, 1993 (Box 116, Folder 26)
  - Wyckoff, Viola, undated (Box 116, Folder 27)
  - Wyman, Katrina, 2002 (Box 116, Folder 28, Box 123, Folder 36)
- Y
  - Yablans, Irwin, 1980 (Box 116, Folder 29)
  - Yablonsky, Ben L., 1953, 1955 (Box 116, Folder 30)
  - Yaeger, undated (Box 116, Folder 31)
  - Yamamoto, Hiroko, undated (Box 116, Folder 32)
  - Yan, Rong, undated (Box 116, Folder 33)
  - Yanagita, Masako, undated (Box 116, Folder 34)
  - Yannett, Bruce E., undated (Box 116, Folder 35)
  - Yaremko, Mile, circa 1941 (Box 116, Folder 36)
  - Yeager, Leland, undated (Box 116, Folder 37)
  - Yellin, Victor, 1967 (Box 116, Folder 38)
  - Yeltsin, Boris, 1991 (Box 116, Folder 39)
  - Yelverton, Ann-Kelly, undated (Box 116, Folder 40)
  - Yin, George, undated (Box 116, Folder 41)
  - Yolles, Dr. Stanley F., 1964 (Box 116, Folder 42)
  - Yonteff-Wolfe, Ruth, 1951 (Box 116, Folder 43)
  - Yoon, Dr. B. Man, undated (Box 116, Folder 44)
  - York, Susannah, undated (Box 116, Folder 45)
  - Yost, Eddie, undated (Box 124, Folder 7)
  - Young, 1986 (Box 116, Folder 46)
  - Young, Alison, undated (Box 116, Folder 47)
  - Young, Henry, undated (Box 116, Folder 48)
  - Young, Lewis, undated (Box 116, Folder 49)
  - Young, Marilyn, undated (Box 124, Folder 8)
  - Young, Percy S., undated (Box 116, Folder 50)
  - Young, Robin, undated (Box 116, Folder 51)
  - Younger, Irving, undated (Box 116, Folder 52)
  - Yu, Mu-Te, undated (Box 116, Folder 53)
  - Yu, Sarah, undated (Box 116, Folder 54)
  - Yushkowski, Joseph, undated (Box 116, Folder 55)
- Z
  - Z, John, undated (Box 116, Folder 56)
  - Zabinsky, Leo, 1979 (Box 116, Folder 57)
  - Zabriskie, Peter, undated (Box 116, Folder 58)
  - Zacharewitz, Sally, undated (Box 124, Folder 9)
  - Zak, Edward, undated (Box 116, Folder 59)
  - Zakkay, Victor, 1982 (Box 116, Folder 60)
  - Zamor, Sheila, 1987 (Box 116, Folder 61)
  - Zand, Dale E., 1954-1985 (Box 116, Folder 62)
  - Zaremba, Peter, 1932
    - Photographs (Box 116, Folder 63)
    - Negatives (Box 124, Folder 10)
  - Zartman, I. William, undated (Box 116, Folder 64)
  - Zavelle, Alexander, 1960-1961 (Box 116, Folder 65)
  - Zazula, 1973 (Box 116, Folder 66)
  - Zeidman, Steven, undated (Box 116, Folder 67)
  - Zeigler, Warren, 1958 (Box 116, Folder 68)
  - Zeller, Daniel, circa 1936 (Box 116, Folder 69)
  - Zemel, Eitan, undated (Box 116, Folder 70)
  - Zerilli-Marimo, Baroness Mariuccia, 1992 (Box 116, Folder 71)
  - Zhang, Jiping, undated (Box 116, Folder 72)
  - Zhang, Qiang, undated (Box 116, Folder 73)
  - Zi, Pepe, undated (Box 116, Folder 74)
  - Zimmer, Lawrence, undated (Box 116, Folder 75)
  - Zimmerman, Diane, 1983, 1989 (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Zimmerman, Jon, undated (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - Zimmerman, Rae, 1980, 1983-1984 (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - Zingman, Shana, 1972 (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - Zinn, Christopher, undated (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - Zinnecker, Wesley, undated (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - Ziobrowski, Stasia, undated (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - Ziskin, James, undated (Box 117, Folder 8)
  - Zito, Frank R., undated (Box 117, Folder 9)
  - Zitran, Arthur, undated (Box 117, Folder 10)
  - Zolt, Eric, 1994 (Box 117, Folder 11)
  - Zorbaugh, Geraldine, undated (Box 117, Folder 12)
  - Zorbaugh, Harvey W., 1962 (Box 117, Folder 13)
  - Zuaro, Al, 1953, 1964 (Box 117, Folder 14)
  - Zubli, Leslie, 1982 (Box 117, Folder 15)
  - Zuckerman, Aron, undated (Box 117, Folder 16)
  - Zuckerman, Mortimer B., undated (Box 117, Folder 17)
  - Zulli, Floyd, 1957, 1963, 1967, 1973 (Box 117, Folder 18)
  - Zumino, Bruno, 1961 (Box 117, Folder 19)
  - Zurcher, Arnold, undated (Box 117, Folder 20)
  - Zwerling, Stephen, 1980 (Box 117, Folder 21)